Tyler Baxter

Lima, Ohio • +1 419-604-0768 • Ty.baxtr@gmail.com • linkedin.com/in/https://www.linkedin.com/tybaxter12/

Information Technology Support

Friendly, and dependable customer service professional with over 2 years of experience. Well versed in administragive duties, problem-solving, planning, and time management. Experienced with working in fast-paced environments and working directly with a diverse range of clients. Also, has knowledge in handling confidential matters and proprietary information.

CERTIFICATIONS

Life Insurance License

State of Ohio Apprenticeship Council

Jan 2021 - May 2022

State of Ohio

Electrician

Apr 2016 - May 2021

CPR

American Red Cross

SKILLS & INTERESTS

Technical Skills: Customer Communication Management, Customer Service, Documentation, Hardware Knowledge, Microsoft 365, Network Basics, Software Installation & Configuration, Technical Troubleshooting

Soft Skills: Adaptability, Attention to Detail, Dependability, Friendliness, Interpersonal Skills, Planning/Processing, Prioritization, Problem Solving, Time Management

Hobbies: Backpacking, Camping, Circuit Racing, Continuous Education, Drift Racing, Hiking, Video Game Development, Video Game Testing

Personality Interests: Computer Hardware Enthusiast, Meditation, Robotics, Technology Advancements, Traveling

WORK EXPERIENCE

Journeyman Electrician • Dayton, OH • Full-time IBEW LU 82

Jul 2023 - Present

International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers

- Licensed in the state of Ohio as a Journeyman Electrician
- · Experience in Residential, Commercial, and Industrial electrician installations
- Reading schematics and laying out installations for employees. Received positive feedback and commendation from clients

Sr. Field Underwriter • Lima, OH, USA

Jan 2022 - May 2023

Equis Financial

- · Daily interpersonal people skills
- Schedule and coordinate meetings with clients daily
- Communicate with clients about their mortgage protection options
- Help clients complete and submit applications to carriers and follow through the underwriting process
- · Service client future policy needs

Journey Electrician • Lima, OH, USA

Ibew Lu 32

- Licensed in the state of Ohio as a Journeyman Electrician
- Experience in Residential, Commercial, and Industrial electrician installations
- Reading & Writing Schematics
- Proficient with the direct installation of wiring at construction and other sites
- · State Electrician License in Ohio
- · CPR Certified

EDUCATION

Electrical in Journeyman Electrician

NJATC - National Joint Apprenticeship Training Center • Lima, OH • GPA: 2nd in Class

Apr 2016 - Apr 2022

Apr 2016 - May 2022

Northwest Community College curriculum partnership

High School Graduate in Basic Study

Bath High school • Lima, OH

Aug 2009 - May 2013